Budget Records, 1987-1989
Smithsonian Institution Archives
Budget Records
1987-1989
Smithsonian Institution Archives, Washington, D.C., osiaref@si.edu
Smithsonian Institution, Assistant Secretary for Research
SI Records
2 cu. ft. (2 record storage boxes)
Accession 90-162
Descriptive Entry
This accession consists of records pertaining to budget planning, requisitions to Congress on budgetary formulations, and priorities for distributing funds to the museums. Materials include correspondence, memoranda, congressional budget submissions (narrative), federal budget requests, trust fund information, employment plan worksheets, and Senate hearing materials.
Index Terms
This collection is indexed under the following access terms. These are links to collections with related topics, persons or places.
Subject
Museums -- Administration.; Budget.; Budget process; Museum finance.
Physical Characteristics of Materials in the Collection
Manuscripts
- Box 1
  - Assist. Secretary Priority Recommendations (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal Budget (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Budget to Congress (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Budget Narratives (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Congressional Action (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Congressional Hearing Materials (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 First Quarter Trust Funds (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Planning Formulation (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Plans Priorities (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Repair Renovation (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Senate Hearings (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Trust Fund Requests (from Contingency) (Box 1 of 2)
  - Unrestricted Trust Budget (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - Archives of American Art (AAA) (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - Conservation Analytical Laboratory (CAL) (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - Cooper-Hewitt Museum (CHM) (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Trust - CHM (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - Horticulture (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - IAC (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Trust - IAC (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - International Environmental Sciences Program (IESP) (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - Joseph Henry Papers (JHP) (Box 1 of 2)
  - Museum Support Center (MSC) Priorities (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - National Air and Space Museum (NASM) (Box 1 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Trust - NASM (Box 1 of 2)
- Box 2
  - FY 1989 Federal - National Museum of American Art (NMAA) (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - National Museum of African Art (NMAfA) (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - National Museum of Natural History (NMNH) (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Trust - NMNH (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - National Portrait Gallery (NPG) (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - National Zoological Park (NZP) (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Trust - NZP (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - Office of American Studies (OAMERS) (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - Office of Fellowships and Grants (OFG) (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Trust - OFG (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - Sackler (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - Smithsonian Astrophysical Observatory (SAO) (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Trust - SAO (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - Smithsonian Environmental Research Center (SERC) (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Trust - SERC (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - Smithsonian Institution Archives (SIA) (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Trust - SIA (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - Smithsonian Institution Libraries (SIL) (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Trust - SIL (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Federal - Smithsonian Tropical Research Institute (STRI) (Box 2 of 2)
  - FY 1989 Trust - STRI (Box 2 of 2)